# Ce Lin

#### Singapore

- Email me on Indeed: <a href="http://www.indeed.com/r/Ce-Lin/6dfe09d31496cf3a">http://www.indeed.com/r/Ce-Lin/6dfe09d31496cf3a</a>

Self-motivated master's student in machine learning and data Science, with enormous curiosity and passion for learning. Worked as a back-end developer with recognized capability in both technical and project management capabilities. Recognized for ability and tenacity to coordinate and execute the data-driven process to tackle and solve the hardest problems during work.

# Work Experience

#### Data Scientist(Intern)

IBM - Singapore August 2018 to March 2019

#### **Backend Developer**

58.com - Beijing May 2016 to December 2017

#### Education

### Master of Technology in Knowledge Engineering(Intelligent System)

National University of Singapore - Singapore January 2018 to Present

## **B.Eng in Software Engineering**

Huazhong University of Science and Technology - Wuhan September 2011 to June 2015

#### Skills

Data Science (1 year), Machine Learning (1 year), Software Development (2 years)

#### Links

https://gradsingapore.com/graduate-employers/ibm/graduate-stories/lin-ce

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ce-lin/?locale=en US